Let's look at the format that is
needed for your target data.
This target data is sometimes also
called categories data or feature
data.
This data may either be a tab in
your Google spreadsheet or it may
be a CSV file.
In both cases, the format is the
same.
First of all, there are four
important column headers.
Category, name, and then min and
max.
In the category column, we have
the list of categories that we're
going to use for our targets.
So in this case, we've got gender,
we've got age bucket, we've got
ethnicity, and we've got
disability.
Under name, we have each of the
possible values that these
categories can take.
So for the gender category, our
possible values are female, male,
and non -binary or other.
And then finally, we have
numerical values, which will be
the minimum and maximum targets
for each of those values.
So for instance, in this sample,
we have a minimum of 10 and a
maximum of 11 for the female value
of the gender category.
Okay, so that's the basic format.
There is one other thing to check.
So in this example, we're
imagining that we're going to
select 20 people.
It's very important that the sum
of the minimums for each category
is less than or equal to 20, and
the sum of the maximums is greater
than or equal to 20.
Let me show you what I mean.
If I highlight all the minimums in
my gender category, then the sum
appears down the bottom here, and
that sum is 10 plus 9 plus 0.
It's 19.
This is less than or equal to 20,
so we're okay.
If I check again, for the age
bucket minimums, I get 17.
For the ethnicity minimums, I get
17.
And for the disability minimums, I
get 19.
All of them were less than or
equal to 20, so that's good.
Let's check the maximums.
For gender, my maximums add up to
22.
For age buckets, 23.
For ethnicity, 22.
And finally, for disability, the
maximums add up to 21.
So in every single case, the sum
of my maximums was greater than or
equal to 20, and so everything is
satisfied.
I have what we call coherent
targets, and I am good to go.